Biggest red flag on a first date? Ugly
shoes.
>> If someone is trying to win you over, do
they need to impress you or Kuma first?
>> If they win Kuma's heart, that's a
faster way for you because he only loves
me.
>> Would you double text?
>> even best days. I'm Willa Bennett and
this is Blind Date.
>> So, normally I go on blind dates, but
[music]
when I chose Jenny as our cover star, I
was like, "Oh my god, you have to open
[music] season 4 of Blind Date." And
she's on the show, so no blindfold
necessary. [music] Please welcome Jenny.
>> Hello.
>> Yes, Jenny, welcome to Blind Date.
>> Hi. I dressed up for you.
>> You did. You look so beautiful.
>> Cheers.
>> Cheers. Welcome to Blind Date.
>> Thank you for having me.
>> My first question for you is, should I
go by Willa, no last name, all caps?
>> Always.
>> Always, you should. I mean, I go by
Jenny, all cap, no last name, so
join the family.
>> I'm just trying to be like you.
>> I think it works with your
everything.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you. You've had a major summer, so
many incredible performances. How are
you feeling watching them, looking back
at them?
>> It was a great summer. I feel like I'm
still here. I'm just having fun and more
exploring of myself and my music, so
it's it's been really fun. And seeing
all the fans around the world, always a
pleasure.
>> Okay, so reader questions will be
fantastic.
>> Hello.
>> Um thank you so much. These are our
incredible readers have many questions
for you. I'm also going in blind, blind
date.
>> Okay.
>> So, let's dig in.
>> [music]
>> You rap, sing, act, and dance. What
percentage of each category are you made
up of?
>> Oh.
A good 25 of each. I want to be able to
face all four of them in the same
energy, [music] you know. I'm 5% dance.
I was I was a dancer for a long time. I
know. If you could add one new skill
into this, what would you pick? Anything
in the world.
>> I want to be a professional bartender.
>> I love that. What is the first drink you
want to make?
>> I don't know. I feel like I've read
stuff on the internet too much where I
believe that I'm capable of making
cocktail, which I'm
>> You definitely can.
>> But, a nice martini. I'll start there.
>> You can put your mind to it. I feel you
can do anything.
>> I can make you one.
>> [laughter]
>> I would love one. Have you ever had a
cosmopolitan?
>> Not that I recall, but I must have. And
this could be my first. Yes.
>> Okay, when does the Capricorn sign of
you come out?
>> I should know this because I recently
talked to my friends about astrology,
which I'm not so familiar with. They
said
that I'm a workaholic, and that's the
Capricorn side of me.
>> Interesting.
>> trying to embrace that. I'm learning
about astrology these days, so what are
you?
>> Libra.
>> Libra, what's something about you?
>> Very creative. A little bit like it's
too bal- it's like two scales.
>> Oh, very balanced.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Do you think you're balanced?
>> I believe I'm a super balanced person.
That's a fun fact about me. I've been I
think I'm a very balanced person.
>> That's cool. This one's good from a
Cosmo reader. If your friends are
saying, "Shut up, Jenny. Just get in the
car." What are you most likely doing or
talking about?
>> [gasps and laughter]
>> In my head in my head, it's
it's we've been out. It's
>> [music]
>> 2:00 a.m. It's 3:00 a.m. And I'm not
trying to go home. And my friends are
saying, "Shut up, Jenny. Get in the
car."
>> What kind of like party are you? Do you
like to dance? Do you like to stay up
late?
>> I love to dance at a party.
>> Really?
>> I don't go out too often, but when I do,
I'd love to just jump around to music
and dance. I love a good dance party.
>> What was it like seeing Dracula blow up?
>> It made me unexpectedly
super happy. I think I woke up every day
getting these [music] new reactions from
fans. So, I was just so happy that the
song did well cuz it happened so
naturally with Kevin. And also the fact
that I still haven't gotten in a space
with him to shoot Wow, really? No, we
did it over Zoom and video calls cuz he
was in Australia and I was in Korea, but
it worked out perfectly.
>> How did you and Kevin meet?
>> He came to Korea and we had mutual
friends, so we ended up hanging out in
Korea and yeah, just like that.
I've always been a fan of his music, so
we talked about working together, but
it happened with Dracula, so I'm just
really happy. It's an amazing song. It's
everywhere.
>> Doja was also on the cover of Cosmo and
she's also a collaborator with you.
>> I love Doja.
She's just like a walking inspiration
for me. Anything that she does is so
creative and I can already tell that she
put so much time and her vision in it
that she's just an inspiring creature
for me. I love you.
>> Was there a certain song that made you
want to collaborate with her? What was
it that drew you to her?
>> I think it's her energy. I was
immediately drawn to all her videos and
all her music from the beginning, so I I
just knew in deep down like I wanted to
collaborate with her, but with the song
Extra L, that's that's what I was
searching for, a strong feminine energy
that I could have fun with. Who else
better than Doja?
>> Readers and your fans love your
friendship with Lily-Rose Depp. What was
it like teaching her how to be a pop
star? Did you give her any interesting
advice?
>> what though? It was the other way around
where Wow, cuz it was also my act first
acting experience and I got to do it
with Lily and she ended up giving me the
most sweetest advice or just on
anything. And still up to this day,
she's still making sure that I'm good. I
was very grateful to have her by my
side.
>> Do you still remember the dance?
>> Ooh, the The that I picked up probably
in like 3 hours. I don't think it's in
my body, but I can probably do it again
in 3 hours.
>> [laughter]
>> That's amazing. What's the quickest
you've ever had to learn choreography?
>> Sometimes the day of, [music] like at
the shoot, we sometimes just make stuff
up on the spot. We did that a lot for
Blackpink, honestly. Like 30 minutes.
>> [laughter]
>> 30 minutes?
>> Yeah, 30 minutes. But it wasn't for the
whole song, but for a good, like a
minute.
>> Are there any [music] performances that
you look back at now and regret?
>> Never.
>> That's cool.
>> Never. I never want to
>> [music]
>> regret anything that I did, so I want to
be proud.
>> Who is your favorite person to see at a
Chanel show?
>> I mean, I love everyone. I love my
Chanel family. When I see Lily at Chanel
anytime, it's like a a ray of sunshine
to me. Like she makes me feel home. And
and everyone else.
>> I love your friendship with Gracie. I I
loved how she wrote that incredible
piece on you recently.
>> I didn't know she was writing this piece
about me, so when I saw it, [music] I
was in literal tears, and I was actually
screaming a little bit, too.
>> Why?
>> It was just the sweetest thing that
anyone could have done. And Gracie is
such a sweetheart, and same with Lily.
Lily and Gracie and I have honestly have
a great time at Chanel shows together.
We I'm so glad to have the girls with me
there.
>> I love your friendship, and I I it's
really [music] even from my phone
screen, it's like so beautiful and
special.
>> I'm such a big fan of her music and her
as an artist, so to be able to share
this generation together [music] so
closely, I think I'm just very lucky.
>> That's so beautiful. This is from a
Cosmo reader.
>> Okay.
>> Who's concert are you screaming front
row at? Also, it says, "Hi Jennie, I
love you." Just so you know.
>> [laughter]
>> I am at Rosalía's concert screaming
front row. I can't [music] wait to go
watch her Locs tour. It seems amazing. I
love the new album. [music]
>> Do you know the song "Umbrella"? I've
picked up Spanish. It's my goal to like
sing the whole thing without looking at
the lyrics. Would you ever collaborate
with her? Can we expect a
>> A dream. A dream.
>> Did you catch her in Euphoria?
>> I did watch the new new season of
Euphoria and watch her do [music] her
thing.
>> She's so great in it.
>> Amazing. Every time she speaks I'm like,
I don't know what you mean what you're
saying, but I love it.
>> This one is highly specific. I think
you're going to like it. Jenny.
If someone is trying to win you over, do
they need to impress you or Kuma first?
>> Ooh. I would love for them to win my
heart, but if they win Kuma's heart
that's a faster
>> [music]
>> way for you because he only loves me.
Sadly.
>> Is Kuma usually right about people?
>> Always. I trust his instinct better than
mine.
>> Really?
>> I think dogs have special talents to
read people's energy though.
>> Do you travel with Kuma everywhere?
>> No. I don't.
>> So when you're on tour you don't you
don't see Kuma for weeks.
>> I see him for weeks and months. He's
turned 11 now, so I just don't want to
fly him to places and put more pressure
on him. He's got a good happy life back
home, so [music] it's okay.
>> Okay, this one's also great. What is the
longest you've ever lasted in a cold
plunge? [music]
>> A little less than 5 minutes. Like 4
minutes.
>> That's a long time.
>> It's a long time. If you cold plunge,
you should you must know, but it's a
long time. Would you break up with
someone if they couldn't [music]
do a cold plunge?
>> I think eventually I can convince him
enough to cold plunge with me.
>> I love a powerful woman.
Jenny, our readers are so grateful that
you took the time to answer their
questions. [music] And now we're going
to move on to the second section, which
is I go through old Cosmos and we kind
of look how [music]
these issues have aged. For you
we have Rihanna.
July
>> Can I take that home?
>> Of course. It'd be my pleasure to gift
you this. This is from the Ask Cosmo
column from the July 2011 issue. Let's
ask Jenny instead. I usually don't drink
when I go out with my friends, but we
always end up splitting the bill. It
kind of feels unfair.
But should I just suck it up?
>> I don't think I would ever feel like
it's unfair on me to pay for something
that I didn't drink. But I'm out with my
friends, so it's it's for the vibe, if
anything. But if you feel that way, that
means maybe you're not hanging out with
the right group.
>> I agree. I'd also just send my request.
>> Yeah.
>> I'd be like, give me back.
>> What is the perfect first date outfit?
[music] My mom says I should always wear
heels. But is that too much?
>> Be you, though. Cuz me, see, I'm not
really a heel
>> Me, they're obviously.
>> I love wearing and dressing up in heels.
The most important thing is your
comfort.
>> The guy I'm dating updates his Facebook
status constantly, but he takes hours to
respond to my texts.
>> No, red flag.
>> Does that mean he isn't into me?
>> He changes his Facebook status, but he's
not replying back to you? Everything
about that is wrong. We need respect and
love from the man.
>> Follow up, would you double text?
>> I don't even first text.
>> Same.
>> So, for me to double text,
that's a big that's a big gesture right
there.
>> Okay, so no.
>> In case emergency, unless
>> What's the emergency? You're not texting
me back.
>> [laughter and gasps]
>> If you're not replying back to me for
your own reason, respect. I'll I respect
your time.
>> Facebook status?
>> Facebook status, by the way, is no.
>> I [laughter] agree.
>> I've caught my boyfriend checking out my
roommate, [music] and it makes me feel
weird. Should I confront them, or will
make me seem paranoid?
>> Always confront. Always confront.
>> Really?
>> I think so. First of all, your boyfriend
should not be checking your roommate
out.
>> I agree. That's inappropriate. I think I
would talk to my friend first.
>> Yes, but we don't know if the roommate
is your friend. It could just be a
roommate, you know? Could just be a hot
roommate. Have you ever had a hot
roommate?
>> [laughter]
>> We'll leave it there. What do I do if
every time I hang out with my boyfriend,
I start to feel really jealous? Any
tips?
>> You got to love yourself.
>> You really got to love yourself and
prioritize you. Do you have any advice
for someone who's maybe struggling with
jealousy?
>> I think trust is such an important
foundation of a relationship that you
should you should learn to trust the
other
and also learn to gain your trust from
the other. So, once that's settled, the
rest is so easy. So, you got to
prioritize the way you see someone, I
think. It's more than chasing. Like, you
you really got to
earn the trust.
>> You're so so eloquent about giving
advice. You should
>> Really?
>> Yeah, you're amazing at it. You should
have a Cosmo column.
>> You're too sweet. Thank you.
>> July 2011. Thank you, Jennie.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Now, to end our incredible date, we're
going to do a love audit, which is super
fun. I'm going to spitball some things,
and you're going to respond quickly.
Okay, you got this.
>> I got this.
>> Insane vocals or jaw-dropping dance
break?
>> Insane vocals.
>> Favorite lyrics from one of your songs?
>> From Zen.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm on the edge of my seat in a really
cool way.
>> [gasps]
>> It's shut up, Jennie, get in the car.
>> [laughter]
>> Shut up, Jennie, just get in the car.
So good.
>> just loved by a lot of people, so yes.
She just had to say, "Shut up, Jennie,
just
drink your Cosmo."
>> Yes. Yes.
>> What BLACKPINK song is quoted to you
most often?
>> More than a song, it's usually BLACKPINK
in your area.
>> Surprise drop an album or tease it
slowly?
>> [music]
>> Surprise.
>> Hop on a remix or drop an acoustic
version?
>> Drop an acoustic version.
>> Ooh, that surprises me. Ball gown or
sweats?
>> Sweats.
>> Capybara or hamsters?
>> Oh, capybara. They're the most calming,
zen, peaceful animal in the world.
>> I always try to learn from capybaras.
The zenness of it, you know?
>> Date [clears throat] a dog person or a
cat person?
>> Dog. Dog.
>> Is it ever okay to go through someone's
phone?
>> No.
>> Date a super fan or someone who has
never heard of your music?
>> Someone who's never heard of my music.
>> What does it mean to be a Cosmo girl?
>> Iconic.
>> I agree.
Keep it mysterious or overshare?
>> Mysterious. We're ladies here.
>> Biggest red flag on a first date?
>> Ugly shoes.
>> Cute or cringe? Joint breakup
statements.
>> I have no clue what
>> So on Instagram you can share a collab
post, you can like collaborate with
someone. So you like collaborate with
someone you're breaking up with and you
give a statement.
>> What?
>> [laughter]
>> You're crazy.
>> Love at first sight or friends to
lovers?
>> I'm leaning towards two.
Friends first.
>> Aw. I think it builds something special.
[music]
>> What is your ideal first date? Drinks,
coffee, dinner, or an activity?
>> Tea.
>> That wasn't one of the
options.
So I have one last question for you.
Will you go on another blind date with
me?
>> Mhm.
>> [gasps]
>> Of course. Of course.
>> I will wear nicer shoes next time.
>> No, you have you have cute shoes.
>> This is the most hectic and chaotic but
real interview that I've ever done.
Thanks to you.
>> Thank you.
>> [music]
>> Ah.
Ah.